jobpost123.com 2011-10-04

# JobPost123.com

**_[Jobpost123.com](http://www.jobpost123.com/)  Privacy Policy_**

This website [Jobpost123.com](http://www.jobpost123.com/)  is committed to protecting the private information of our web site visitors.  This website adheres to a strict policy for ensuring the privacy of personally identifiable information and preserving the integrity of this online medium.  Here we explain the type of information collected from website, how that information may be used, how you can access or modify that information, and how that information is protected.   

WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
We collect two types of information from visitors to the Site:  (A) Personally Information, and (B) Non-personal Information (information such as IP Addresses and cookies, which allow for a better use of the Site). 

We will not collect personally identifiable information from you, other than what you supply to us on a voluntary basis upon request.  Personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, name, address, e-mail address, telephone number.

COOKIES 

A cookie will tell us which pages you visit and the amount of time between each page visit.  The cookie does not remember any information about you or your computer; it just helps us at This website monitor Site usage and traffic; for example, it allows us to measure the number of repeat visitors to website in a given month. This data is only used in the aggregate.

**What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?**   
The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.  
Your privacy policy should include the following information:

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).) 

HOW IS MY INFORMATION PROTECTED?  
This website is committed to ensuring the security of the data provided to us by Site users.  To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect online.

TERMS OF USE  
Please also make sure to read our TERMS OF USE to understand the additional terms and conditions which apply to your use of our Site. 

CONTACT  
Send email to use if you are having any additional points / questions.
